Guide to the Stanford Parents' Club Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Parents' Club records
1923-2009
SC0261
Mothers’ Club of Stanford University
Stanford Parents Club..
21 Linear feet (34 boxes)
The records include minutes, 1923-2007; records pertaining to fellowships, scholarships and awards, 1957-1969; a history notebook, 1924-1973; scrapbooks, 1930-1985; records concerning the Chrysanthemum Party (annual fund raiser), 1963-1989; files pertaining to the Men's Rest Home,1931-1945, and the Women's Rest Home, 1928-1945; and miscellaneous financial records, publicity materials, and membership records, 1933-2009.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
The records were received by the University Archives via administrative transfers from the Stanford Parents' Club in 1981, 1993, 1996, 1997, 1998, 2001, and 2009.
Information about Access
Portions of this collection contain protected health information (PHI) as defined by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPPA) of 1996. Access is therefore restricted. Patrons who wish to access materials from this collection must consult the Special Collections and University Archives Access to Health Information of Individuals Policy at http://library.stanford.edu/depts/spc/pubserv/access_to_health_policy.pdf.
The collection is otherwise open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Stanford Parents' Club, first organized in 1923 as the Stanford Mothers' Club, provides financial and social assistance to Stanford students; from 1924 to 1962 they operated student convalescent facilities known as Rest Homes.
Description of the Collection
The records include minutes, 1923-2007; records pertaining to fellowships, scholarships and awards, 1957-1969; a history notebook, 1924-1973; scrapbooks, 1930-1985; records concerning the Chrysanthemum Party (annual fund raiser), 1963-1989; files pertaining to the Men's Rest Home,1931-1945, and the Women's Rest Home, 1928-1945; and miscellaneous financial records, publicity materials, and membership records, 1933-2009.
Access Terms
Mothers’ Club of Stanford University; Stanford Mothers' Club.; Stanford Parents Club..; Stanford University -- General subdivision--Students.
Collection Contents
- Original Records, Series 1
  - Meeting minutes, 1923-1932 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes, 1932-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting minutes, 1936-1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting minutes, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Meeting minutes, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting minutes, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Meeting minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meeting minutes, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Meeting minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Meeting minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Meeting minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Meeting minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Meeting minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Meeting minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Meeting minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Meeting minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Meeting minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Meeting minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Meeting minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Meeting minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Meeting minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Meeting minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Meeting minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Meeting minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Meeting minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Meeting minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Meeting minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Meeting minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Meeting minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Meeting minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Meeting minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Stanford University Annual Financial Report, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Fellowships, scholarships, awards, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Fellowships, scholarships, awards, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Fellowships, scholarships, awards, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Fellowships, scholarships, awards, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Fellowships, scholarships, awards, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Fellowships, scholarships, awards, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Fellowships, scholarships, awards, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Fellowships, scholarships, awards, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Fellowships, scholarships, awards, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Fellowships, scholarships, awards, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Fellowships, scholarships, awards, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - History notebooks, 1924-1931 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - History notebooks, 1931-1932 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - History notebooks, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - History notebooks, 1939-1952 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - History notebooks, 1952-1960 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - History notebooks, 1960-1967 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - History notebooks, 1967-1973 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Oversize item; relocated to Box 12 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Scrapbooks, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Scrapbooks, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Scrapbooks, 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Scrapbooks, 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Scrapbooks, 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Scrapbooks, 1938-1940 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Scrapbooks, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Oversize item; relocated to Box 12 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Scrapbooks, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Scrapbooks, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Scrapbooks, 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Yearbook, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Special financial records ledger, 1935-1941 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Oversize item; relocated to Box 12 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Oversize item; relocated to Box 12 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Treasurer's notebook, 1954-1965 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Rest Home reports, 1957-1962 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Chrysanthemum Tea reports, 1963-1968 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Chrysanthemum Tea photos, 1965-1970 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Library Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Publicity scrapbook, 1946-1953 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Men's Rest Home files, 1931-1934 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Men's Rest Home files, 1934-1936 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Men's Rest Home files, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Men's Rest Home files, 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Men's Rest Home files, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Men's Rest Home files, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Men's Rest Home files, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Men's Rest Home files, 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Men's Rest Home files, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1928-1932 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1932-1934 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1942-1943 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Women's Rest Home files, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Lease for Men's Rest Home (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Lease for Women's Rest Home (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Agreement for Rest Home directors, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Rest Home financial reports, 1930-1935 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Rest Home regulations and miscellaneous reports and correspondence, 1946-1953 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Publicity scrapbook, 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Publicity scrapbook, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Newcomers registration book, 1950-1958 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Newcomers registration book, 1950-1958 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Form letters to parents of students with programs of club activities, 1938-1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, 1958-1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - History of the Club by Marian Hall and correspondence pertaining to club history, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "Campus Cavalcade" by Dorothy Nichols [pageant on University's history], circa 1939 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous letters and programs, 1933-1975 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1993-136
  - Notebooks containing lists, reports, clippings, fliers, financial records, photographs, and correspondence pertaining to the annual Chrysanthemum Party, 1976-1984 (Box 1)
  - Staff reports, 1977-1982 (Box 1)
  - Publicity materials (copies of press releases and clipping), 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - Three scrapbooks containing clippings, brochures, photographs, reports, fliers, and other items on the activities of the Club, 1980-1985 (Box 2)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1996-038
  - Articles of Incorporation and By-Laws of the Mothers Club, 1940-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Tax papers, 1966-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Tax papers, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Tax papers, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Paid bills, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bank statements, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer's report, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bank statement, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Deposit record, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Paid bills, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Tax return, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer's report, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Paid bills, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Deposit slips/summary of income, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer's report, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bank statement, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Expense receipts, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Treasurer's report, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Deposit record, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bank statement, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Benefits money handling: Chrysanthemum Party, 1975-1986; Designer Doorways, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Expense receipts, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Deposit record, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bank statement, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - State sales tax forms, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Blank Wells Fargo check book (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Expense record, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Income record, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bank statement - money market account, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bank statement - checking account, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer's report, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Tax return, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1996-130
  - 1940s Letters; Foreign Letters; Tours; Mothers Club Sections. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Regarding Admissions Tax ($.01 for each $.05 collected), 1946 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - By-laws and Policies, 1936-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Pictures (Mrs. Ann Sterling) and reply from Mrs. Edmund Brown, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Financial Accounting for Benefits, etc. given, 1965-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board Rosters (some missing), 1954-1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Collection of "TEA" articles, 1965-1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Publicity and clippings, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Clippings (pictures - a silver tray, etc.), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Hospitality, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Publicity, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Tea, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Golden Jubilee, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Presidents' Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Publicity, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Hors-d'oeuvres, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Chrysanthemum Party, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Presidents' letters, etc., 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 34 "pink" slip deposit record books, 1981-1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Financial Report Deposit Summary, 1980-1981, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Job Description, 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Job Description, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - News item: "Stanford in Washington", 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Financial Report re Phantom Party (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Chrysanthemum Tea, articles and pictures, 1967 Nov 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Job Reports, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Loose clippings and pictures, miscellaneous letters and reports, 1963-1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Tea and Trip Souvenirs, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Alpine Infirmary (picture) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bi-Annual Presidents' Letters and Programs, 1948-1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Packet of Correspondence Notes (over many years), Mrs. (Governor) Edmund G. Brown and others (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Analysis Columnar Pads, 1981-1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Picture of Ray Lyman Wilbur (President of Stanford (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - January 1, 1916-January 1, 1942), 1941 Jun 23
  - Chrysanthemum Posters, 1973-1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Originals of the 1977 spring mailing - Letter and Program (mock up before the days of computers, etc.) (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1997-098
  - President Rosenna Yau's file - front matter, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - President Rosenna Yau's file - budgets, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - President Rosenna Yau's file - minutes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - President Rosenna Yau's file - Friends of H & S, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - President Rosenna Yau's file - job descriptions, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - President Rosenna Yau's file - members and past presidents, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - President Rosenna Yau's file - correspondence/notes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - President Rosenna Yau's file - miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Freshman transfer party, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Association Office (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Parent notification correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - August Letter, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Printer (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - January Mailing, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Stanford support groups (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Telephone communication lists (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Publications - includes Gourmet Recipes from Early Days in California 1891-1991 in Honor of the Stanford Centennial (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Scholarships (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Birthday cake services (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Public Service Fellowship Program, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Public service, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Public Service Fellow, 1992 summer (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Job descriptions, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Job descriptions, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chrysanthemum Tea, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1985-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1983-1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Harriet Bloom, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - To Do (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Fashion Show, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
  - Fashion Show (more materials) (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Presidents' letters and enclosures (Elzene Yancey, Dee Heinze, Eleanor Torgerson, B. J. Darrow, Bernice Holubar, Helen Seethaler), 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Parents Fund (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - By-laws, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Program reports (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Printing reports, 1980-1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - B. J. Darrow miscellaneous, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Video: Stanford at the Crossroads: with President Donald Kennedy and Trustee George Hume, 1991 Nov (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 3-ring binder with appliqued cloth cover (Box 4)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1998-208
  - Listing of the Board of Directors, 1942-1998 (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2001-295
  - Photograph and ephemera album, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Taste of Red and White Notebook, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1993-1997 (Box 1)
  - Board members, 1940-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Chrysanthemum Party publicity, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Designer Showcase, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Publicity, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dessert social with President and Mrs. Clinton, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Financial Report, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Publications, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Thank-yous, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Articles of Incorporation, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    This folder also includes a memo from the Stanford Parents Club dated November 2009, which clarifies that the By-laws and Amendments to Articles of Incorporation stapled to the Certificate of Amendment of Articles of Incorporation in this folder were never officially adopted.
  - Clippings and publicity, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Financial Report and Board of Directors, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Publications, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Casper, Gerhard, letter, 1999 Oct 15 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Financial Report, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Photographs, 1990-2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Publications, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2005-207
  - Recording secretary expenses, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Financial secretary expenses, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Financial secretary, accounts, 1995 quarter 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Financial secretary, accounts, 1995 quarter 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Financial secretary, accounts, 1996 quarter 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Financial secretary, accounts, 1996 quarter 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Financial records, 1996-1997 quarters 1 and 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Financial records, 1996-1997 quarters 3 and 4 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Financial records, 1997-1998 quarters 1 and 2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Financial records, 1997-1998 quarters 1 and 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Deposit records (incomplete), 1993-1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2009-065
  - Minutes and Agendas, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes and Agendas, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes and Agendas, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    This folder also includes a memo from the Stanford Parents Club dated November 2009, which clarifies that the By-laws and Amendments to Articles of Incorporation filed under August 1999 in this folder were never officially adopted.
  - Minutes and Agendas, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and Agendas, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minutes and Agendas, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and Agendas, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes and Agendas, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes and Agendas, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes and Agendas, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes and Agendas, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous pamphlets and programs, 2003-2009 (Box 1, Folder 12)